German Huayhua Condori

Software Engineer - Full Stack Developer

☑ yhermmany@gmail.com

github.com/hcgerman

inkedin.com/in/hcgerman

About me

Software developer with experience in web development. I have worked for more than 4 years in technology companies in backend and full stack developer roles. I am responsible and kind. I consider myself a communicative person willing to work in a team, efficient in the achievements, goals and objectives set by the company.

Relevant Experience

Full Stack Developer @ Notus SpA

Oct 2021 - Present // Santiago, Chile

- ▶ Write modern, performant, and robust code for a diverse array of client and internal projects
- ▶ Development of geospatial models, maps and GIS software with python.
- ▶ Development of Api RESTful and Web Applications with Django and testdriven development with pytest.
- ▶ Implementation of Docker, Kubernetes and flows with Argo Workflows.
- ▶ Communicate and collaborate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, clients, and stakeholders on a daily basis.

Backend Developer @ tuGerente

April 2020 - September 2021 // Santa Cruz, Bolivia

- ▶ Development of ERP system, python modules, Django projects, Node JS projects and React JS projects.
- ▶ Design and development of distributed applications using sockets and web services.
- ▶ Dockerization of applications.
- ▶ Work with a variety of different languages, frameworks, and content management systems such as JavaScript, React, Vue, Node.js, Express JS, Python, Django, Shopify, WordPress, etc.
- ▶ Development of automated tests with TDD.
- Integrations with external services such as Shopify, Woocommerce, Pedidos Ya, among others.

Full Stack Developer @ Ticketeg S.R.L.

February 2018 - March 2020 // Santa Cruz, Bolivia

- ▶ Development of payment platform and event management system.
- ▶ Design and development of web applications using Django and Ruby on
- ▶ Development of automated tests with TDD.
- ▶ Design and development of mobile applications with React Native projects on Android and IOS.
- ▶ Implementation of Web Services such as SOAP, RESTful and Graphql.

Skills

Programming Languages

Python, Ruby, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript

Libraries & Frameworks

Diango, Ruby on Rails, React JS, React Native, Next.js, Express, Jekyll

Tools & Platforms

Git, Heroku, Amazon Web Services (EC2, Route 53, S3), Docker, Kubernetes, Argo Workflows, Linux Servers, Node JS + Express

Education

CBA (Centro Boliviano Americano)

2019 - Present // Santa Cruz, BO English Course - Intermediate Level

UAGRM (Universidad Autonoma Gabriel Rene Moreno)

2018 // Santa Cruz, BO Business Systems Management 2013 - 2018 // Santa Cruz, BO Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Interests

Reading, traveling, attend online and face-to-face training, go fishing, watch movies with the family.